Rashid Masood

009-715-6350167 rashikhankhan557@gmail.com Sharjah Al Majaz 1 UAE Zip 500001

SUMMARY

I am a Journeyman Electrician currently residing in the U.A.E. with 8 years of domestic/commercial experience in the installation, repair, and maintenance of HVAC and LVAC electrical systems. I perform duties with the highest quality and efficiency and ensure that work is in accordance with relevant codes. I am well-versed in electrical regulations, ensuring the highest level of safety and compliance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

MAINTENANCE TECHNICIAN Apr 2018 - Oct 2022

IMANCO SANITARY WARE TR L.L.C Sharjah, United Arab Emirates

INDUSTRIAL ELECTRICAL TECHNICIAN Nov 2015 - Nov 2017

PAK LINK SERVICES L.L.C Dubai, United Arab Emirates

INSTALLATION ELECTRICIAN Nov 2012 - Nov 2014

HASSAN HASHIM TECHNICAL SERVICES Dubai, United Arab Emirates

TASKS/RESPONSIBILITIES

Electrical:

- Installs and repairs electrical equipment and fixtures
- Bending conduit, cable tray fixing, wall chaser
- Install and repair sub panels, lighting, wiring, switches gears, socket, circuit breakers
- Glanding termination of MDB and SMDB dressing, install/repair
- 3 phase and single phase wiring and troubleshooting, Earthing
- Submersible, Injector, Circulation and Booster pump install and repair
- Electric heat tracing, Heating wire installation, Maintenance and commissioning
- Identifies all material, equipment needed to complete the project
- AC Motor Installation/Maintenance/Repair
- Electrical Renovation/Remodeling

Plumbing:

- PPR Pipe: Domestic piping and plumbing fitting for water supply
- Maintenance of water supply system
- Electric water heater installation/maintenance
- Replacing wash basin, taps and toilet

TECHNICAL EDUCATION

INDUSTRIAL ELECTRICIAN Feb 2009 - Feb 2010

PUNJAB VOCATIONAL TRAINING COUNCIL Lahore

MATRICULATION IN SCIENCE Jun 2006 - Aug 2008

CITY DISTRICT, GOVT. BOYS HIGH SCHOOL Lahore

PROFESSIONAL CREDENTIALS

INDUSTRIAL ELECTRICIAN 20 July 2010
Government of the Punjab Lahore